{
    "id": "53b9a3d95d574e4ba3fb2f549aabc086",
    "title": "Change Into Past Tense",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He writes to his mother every week. / He ................... to his mother every week.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wrote",
                "was writing",
                "had written"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He walks fast. / He ..................... fast.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "walked",
                "walking",
                "was walking"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The castle stands on the hill. / The castle .................. on the hill.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "had stood",
                "stood",
                "was standing"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He gets up at six oâ€™clock. / He .................. up at six o'clock.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was getting",
                "would get",
                "got"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He spends his time in idle pursuits. / He .................. his time in idle pursuits.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "spending",
                "spent",
                "had spent"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Mark studies very well. / Mark ................. very well.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was studying",
                "had studied",
                "would study",
                "studied"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "He earns 200 dollars a week. / He ................. 200 dollars a week.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was earning",
                "earned",
                "had earned"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "What strikes me is the generosity of the offer. / What .................... me was the generosity of the offer.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "struck",
                "had struck",
                "striked"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He sows the seeds of dissension. / He ..................... the seeds of dissension.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "sowed",
                "sown",
                "had sown"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She leaves her things on the table. / She ....................... her things on the table.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "leaved",
                "left",
                "had left"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "They all tell the same story. / They all ..................... the same story.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "telled",
                "told",
                "telling"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "People mistake him for an American. / People ................ him for an American.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "mistaked",
                "mistaken",
                "mistook"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He throws cold water on my plans. / He ...................... cold water on my plans.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "throwed",
                "threw",
                "thrown"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Trees shed their leaves in the autumn. / Trees ....................... their leaves in the autumn.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "shed",
                "sheded",
                "shedding"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}